{
    "subject": "resource/Fabio_Testi",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Fabio Testi (born 2 August 1941) is an Italian film actor, notable as the star of, among many other films, First Action Hero.Born in Peschiera del Garda, Italy, the 1.84m tall actor started his film career as a stuntman in his college years. His most famous job as a stuntman was in Sergio Leone's Once Upon a Time in the West, where he fell from a rooftop and hit the ground on his shoulder.He has a son, Edwin, born 1971, from his relationship with Edwige Fenech. In 1979 Testi married Lola Navarro, with whom he fathered three children. On January 3, 2015 he got married to Antonella Liguori.",
    "human_readable": "Fabio Testi is an Italian film actor, notable as the star of First Action Hero and other films, born in Peschiera del Garda, Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9361347556114197,
            "question": "Name a film starring Fabio Testi."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9226220846176147,
            "question": "Is Fabio Testi an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8727614879608154,
            "question": "What is the name of one of Fabio Testi's notable films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8446173071861267,
            "question": "Where was Fabio Testi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8221824765205383,
            "question": "In which country was Fabio Testi born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7711441516876221,
            "question": "What is Fabio Testi known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7442024350166321,
            "question": "What nationality is Fabio Testi?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7397480010986328,
            "question": "What is a film genre that Fabio Testi is associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.605191171169281,
            "question": "What type of profession does Fabio Testi have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5458489060401917,
            "question": "Where is Peschiera del Garda located?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Fabio Testi is an Italian film actor, notable as the star of First Action Hero and other films, born in Peschiera del Garda, Italy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_225_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of profession does Fabio Testi have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_225_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is a film genre that Fabio Testi is associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_225_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What nationality is Fabio Testi?",
            "html": "dbpedia_225_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_225_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to evaluate any more triples! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, I can determine that the statement about Fabio Testi is correct. \n\nThe output should be:\n```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThis is because all the documents mention Fabio Testi as an Italian film actor, notable as the star of First Action Hero and other films, born in Peschiera del Garda, Italy, which confirms the statement about him being an Italian film actor, notable for starring in First Action Hero."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided documents contain information about Fabio Testi that supports the statement: \"Fabio Testi is an Italian film actor, notable as the star of First Action Hero and other films, born in Peschiera del Garda, Italy.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}